

Sarun Norrak

Sangkat toul sangke, khan russey keo, phnom penh, cambodia

+855 10 733 062

M sarunnorak1999@gmail.com

in linkedin.com/in/sarun-norak-2938b0191/

ABOUT ME

Creative web developer dedicated to developing and optimizing interactive, user-friendly, and feature-rich websites. Leverage analytical skills and strong attention to detail in order to deliver original and efficient web solutions, provide technical knowledge and expertise, build new websites from start to finish, and successfully manage a team of web developers.

SKILLS & PROFICIENCIES

Languages Skills

- Khmer (Mother tongue)
- English

Web Development Skills

- WordPress
- · MySQL, PHP, Laravel
- · JavaScript, JQuery, JSON, AJAX
- HTML5, CSS3, SASS, Bootstrap
- React JS, Angular JS, Vue.js, Npm
- Nuxt JS, Nest JS

Interpersonal/Life Skills

- Analytical Skills
- Good Team Player
- Multi-tasking

Other Skills

- Adobe Photoshop, illustrator
- · Microsoft office Word, Excel, Access

INTEREST AND LOBBY

- · Machine Learning
- · Video Games, Music, Movies
- · Soccer, Basketball, Cycling

WORK HISTORY

Web Developer and IT assistant

Jian Zhong Realty Co., Ltd.

June 2018 to February 2019

Establish an interactive and dynamic website that guarantees high traffic, page views, and maximum user experience.

WordPress Developer

PA Auto R&C Center.

August 22, 2019 - November 8, 2019

Devised various custom responsive WordPress site from design comps that include advanced WordPress features, such as Custom Post Types, Advanced Custom Fields, and WordPress Customize API.

Front-end Developer

Coolbeans Studio

July 2020 to Present

Developed and structured feature-rich client websites, ensuring that all needs were met and company policies and procedures followed; created high-quality code.

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND

Sovannaphumi School (2016 - 2017)

In 2016 I won the 1st place in English public speaking competition.

WAT Phnom high School

Phnom Penh

Finish high school and graduated in 2017.

Royal University of Phnom Penh

Phnom Penh

Bachelor's Degree in Computer Science, Graduated in 2021.